Babi Kamara Hank Akim Goma, Nord-Kivu, RDC

Email: hnkakim@gmail.com Téléphone: +243 991 898 723

LinkedIn: Hank AKim
Portfolio: Hank Akim



OBJECTIF

Junior Web Developer and Digital Marketing Specialist with experience in web project management and digital content creation. As the Marketing Director of the startup AgroKivu, I aim to apply my expertise in digital campaign management and web development.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

AgroKivu - Goma, RDC

Marketing Director

2018 - Présent

- Participated in the creation of AgroKivu and the development of its marketing strategy.
- Managed the company's LinkedIn page (<u>AgroKivu LinkedIn</u> including content creation and management.
- Designed and implemented online advertising campaigns, particularly on Facebook Ads and Google Analytics, to promote local agricultural products

MaxBounty - Remote

CPI Marketing Specialist

2017 - Present

- Managed and optimized cost-per-install (CPI) marketing campaigns for various clients.
- Analyzed campaign performance and adjusted advertising strategies to maximize results.

General Directorate of Revenues of North Kivu (DGRN-K) – Goma, DRC Junior Web Developer

June 2023 – Present

- Designed and developed over 10 web projects for tax services.
- Optimized and maintained websites to ensure better performance and security.

FONAHD-RDC (NGO)

Freelance Web Consultant

2022 - 2023

- Developed and maintained the NGO's website.
- · Freelance Projects
- Independent Web Developer 2021 2023
- Designed customized websites for various clients.

FORMATION

Université Libre de Kigali – Kigali, Rwanda Bachelor's Degree in Applied Computer Science Graduated in 2022

COMPÉTENCES

- Web Languages: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, MySQL
- Digital Marketing: Facebook Ads, Google Analytics, CPI Marketing
- SEO & Content Management: Content optimization and Product listing management on ecommerce sites
- Databases: MySQL, MariaDBPlatforms: Shopify, WordPress

?

PERSONAL QUALITIES

- Ability to manage multiple content projects simultaneously
- Attention to detail to ensure the accuracy of information on websites
- Strong organizational and time management skills
- Commitment to conservation efforts and supporting local communities

INTERESTS

- Nature conservation and environmental protection
- Information and Communication Technologies (ICT)
- Traveling and cultural exploration

RÉFÉRENCE

- Florent Baziraboba: National Coordinator FONAHD RDC Contact +243 998 865 210 Email fonahdrdc@gmail.com
- Finganduli Firmen: Senior Developer E-mail: finganduli@gmail.com Contact +254 736 881340
- Posho Mbili: IT fonahdrdc Contact +243 894 098 698 E-Mail: possilvie3@gmail.com
- Kyamuva Gérôme : DGRNK Senior Developer (direction générale des recettes du Nord-Kivu)
 Goma, Nord-Kivu, RDC contact + 243 994 401 108 E-Mail : kamkyaj@gmail.com
- Daddy Izinga: Brand strategist/ Marketing strategist & creative director Agrokivu contact +243 902 337 344 E-Mail: phildadizinga@gmail.com